Next up is Moka.
I decided that this was the only way to go.
Chocolate. Sweets.
But isn't that kind of chocolate rare? I had to choose.
I thought we'd be happier if we ate it together.
Together? Wait a minute.
We only have three for everyone.
You mean you're giving them away?
Depends on my mood.
My favorite.
You're assuming Moehka eats one too?
Yes, one for me.
Then you can give it to me.
There's four of us.
So if you can please Moeka...
I'll give it to my favorite member.
My beautiful dream is here
At least my
Wish to come true with you
You are me
Tell me now, it doesn't mean anything
If it's words, I don't need them anymore
Now, now, now, now
That's why I'm good.
By the way, you eat that during the song.
You have to be in a good mood during the song, right?
What do I do?
Shout out Moeka's good points.
Yell?
During the song.
I'll start with this song.
Moe! Challenge music start!
I've got it.
I have a project.
Thank you all for coming today.
It's not fair, it's not fair, it's not fair
We're all dancing together. Everyone dances together.
Moeka-chan, I mean cute Moeka-chan
Let's dance together
It's not fair, it's not fair, it's not fair
Come on!
Hey, already!
You're always dancing.
It's not fair
But I'm singing.
Why don't you write down the lyrics?
What?
Moeka's cute and blonde.
Very petite, T-scene.
I want to hug you.
Yay, yay!
Mouka!
Moeka
Moehwa
Stop it, stop it.
Moehka Moehka Moehka
Cute
You're the best!
Moehana ita ita
I don't want moeka
She wants to eat a little more.
I don't want moka
I don't want mocha.
I can go.
Moehana.
Hurry up and give it to me.
Diva.
You're so cute with big eyes.
You're the best.
Yay!
Moehwa
Moehwa.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, big brother.
I feel good.
I feel so good.
Everyone complimented me.
This is the best project I've ever done.
What a plan!
It's a great plan!
Let's do it again.
What was the criteria?
I couldn't find anything.
These are my favorite members.
Favorite member.
Water.
And now, let's move on.
I'm Aira.
I chose this one.
Osatsudoki
Salted butter flavor
Looks so delicious!
This is my favorite
It's my favorite candy!
Whenever I buy sweets, I buy this one!
I love sweet potatoes.
So I'd like to eat this during the song.
I'd like to eat it during the song.
I think this is still good.
I wanted ramen.
I'll eat it and I won't be able to eat it
I want to eat it and
I think I could go for this.
I chose this one.
I don't know if it'll dissolve a little bit.
I don't know if it'll dissolve if it's still in your mouth in the worst case.
But this kind of thing...
You have to chew it with your teeth and gulp it down.
It's kind of hard. It's a little difficult.
It's a little difficult.
But I'll eat it.
There are songs I can do.
Aira-san sings from the beginning to the end.
She sings a lot, and she doesn't seem to be able to sing.
I can eat.
I'll eat.
I'd like to start with it in my hand.
Hold it.
Okay, let's start the music.
What's with the squirming?
Definitely not the same choreography.
Guys.
Choreography.
This is bad.
Is she singing? Are you singing?
Are they singing?
They're singing.
There's one more guy eating.
It's delicious.
What are you giving it to me for?
No, no, no.
I like it.
We're good.
We've had our moments.
Yes, I'll do it.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I was able to catch the joints when I was singing.
I was able to catch it here.
I'm sure it's not the same choreography.
Catch it on the "tsunagete".
You ate it.
You could have caught the equal and eaten it here.
But, you know... But you know what?
The camera.
I thought I had to appeal to the camera.
I didn't want to give it to Yuzu.
No, I can get it without looking at it.
First position.
Right here, right next to you.
I'll get it right here.
That's where I eat it.
That's not for the flowers.
I'm sorry, I'm not your favorite member.
So you know what?
When we're dancing and I'm patching my fingers...
If I can get the hole...
If I can get it there.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
Hey, you're right, there.
Chacha-chan.
It's Chacha-Cha-Cha's tea.
Chachachan.
So I should just hold it in my flat hand.
No, you should give her one.
If I give it to you like this...
Then, please.
Start the music.
No, no, no.
Not to begin with.
We'll get it soon.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it.
It's coming soon!
I have to get ready too.
I'll be there.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no. No, I can't.
I have the highest difficulty level.
I'm almost there.
But you've got to do this one thing, and I'll tell you why it's not working.
The flowers will eat it.
I've got a hole in me.
If I could take it out...
You're not my favorite member.
Beginner's Bank.
Newbie bank.
I'm a research student
American research student
Yes, so the last one is
Hana-chan!
Hana-chan, what kind of food did you prepare for us?
Yes, I did.
I prepared this...
This is it!
Natto (fermented soybeans)
Natto...
It's good for the immune system.
It's good for your body
I thought it would be easy to eat.
It's true that the sauce makes it soft and tender.
It's true.
I thought it would be easy to eat.
So I decided on natto.
What about the sauce?
Natto is usually served with sauce.
There's no sauce.
Hana-chan
This is the natto Hana-chan bought
Look at this package
There's no sauce and no mustard
What's that?
There is natto these days
Why?
There are a lot of other things, aren't there? There were lots of others, weren't there?
It was the cheapest.
This is why.
Because I was stingy.
In case you're wondering where Hana wanted to eat this natto.
Where did Hana want to eat this natto?
I'd like to see it.
Can you do that?
It's possible.
I'd like to take a look.
Music starts!
Pounding!
Please let the flowers fall in the chorus.
Dori-Sabi
Falling Rust
More later.
I have to sing the "ochi-chi-ni" (fall) part.
It's somewhere around here.
Something's wrong.
What?
It's dirty.
Dirty.